Faculty Reference Collection
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Buck, Red, Undated; nam_ua950.003-325 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Buck, Vernon A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-326 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Budd, Celeste, Undated; nam_ua950.003-327 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Bueche, Arthur M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-328 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Buff, Brian, Undated; nam_ua950.003-329 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Buhrmaster, Kenneth E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-330 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Bulgaro, Patrick J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-331 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Bullis, Daryl, 2000; nam_ua950.003-332 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Bunis, Donald W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-333 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Bunnell, Gene, Undated; nam_ua950.003-334 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Burgess, Robert S., 1946; nam_ua950.003-335 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Burke, Brian, Undated; nam_ua950.003-336 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Burke, Gerald T., 1999; nam_ua950.003-337 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Burke, Joseph C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-338 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Burke, Kevin, Undated; nam_ua950.003-339 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Burke, Kevin, Undated; nam_ua950.003-340 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Burkhart, Louise, Undated; nam_ua950.003-341 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Burleson, Brant R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-342 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Burlin, Dee, Undated; nam_ua950.003-343 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Burlingame, Robert, Undated; nam_ua950.003-344 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Burlingame, Robert Raymond, Undated; nam_ua950.003-345 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Burnette, Thomas C., 1970; nam_ua950.003-346 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Burns, Elizabeth L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-347 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Burrell, Barbara C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-348 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Burrell, Barbara C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-349 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Burrell, Jennifer, Undated; nam_ua950.003-350 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Burrell, William G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-351 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Burt, Ronald S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-352 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Burwell, Jacquelyn, Undated; nam_ua950.003-353 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Busch, F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-354 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Busch, Steven, Undated; nam_ua950.003-355 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Bush, Brian, Undated; nam_ua950.003-356 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Bushweller, C. Hackett, Undated; nam_ua950.003-357 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Butler, Meredith, Undated; nam_ua950.003-358 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Butler, Meredith, Undated; nam_ua950.003-359 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Butler, Meredith, Undated; nam_ua950.003-360 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Butler, Meredith A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-361 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Butler, Timothy J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-362 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Butz, Robert A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-363 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Byng, Dennis, Undated; nam_ua950.003-364 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Byng, Dennis, Undated; nam_ua950.003-365 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Bynum, Terrel W., 1968; nam_ua950.003-366 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Byrne, Donn, Undated; nam_ua950.003-367 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Byrne, Donn, Undated; nam_ua950.003-368 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Cdbury, Warder H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-369 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Calef, Monica Pusher, Undated; nam_ua950.003-370 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Cable, Floyd, Undated; nam_ua950.003-371 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Cadbury, Warder, 1963; nam_ua950.003-372 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Calhoun, Leon Sr., Undated; nam_ua950.003-373 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Calhoun, Leon J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-374 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Cali, Alfred, Undated; nam_ua950.003-375 (Box 5, Folder 65)
- Callahan, William V., Undated; nam_ua950.003-376 (Box 5, Folder 66)
- Calsada, Mathew, 2001; nam_ua950.003-377 (Box 5, Folder 67)
- Camacho, Eduardo, 1971; nam_ua950.003-378 (Box 5, Folder 68)
- Campbell, Lyle R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-379 (Box 5, Folder 69)
- Campbell, Ron, Undated; nam_ua950.003-380 (Box 5, Folder 70)
- Campisi, Jack, nam_ua950.003-381 (Box 5, Folder 71)
- Candlyn, Frederick T., 1964; nam_ua950.003-382 (Box 5, Folder 72)
- Cannon, Harold L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-383 (Box 5, Folder 73)
- Cantrel, Robert, Undated; nam_ua950.003-384 (Box 5, Folder 74)
- Capps, Joan P., Undated; nam_ua950.003-385 (Box 5, Folder 75)
- Cardone, Dianne, Undated; nam_ua950.003-386 (Box 5, Folder 76)
- Carbone, David, Undated; nam_ua950.003-387 (Box 5, Folder 77)
- Carey, Governor, Undated; nam_ua950.003-388 (Box 5, Folder 78)
- Caraco, Thomas, Undated; nam_ua950.003-389 (Box 5, Folder 79)
- Cargill, Mary L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-390 (Box 5, Folder 80)
- Carlock, John E., 1962-1975; nam_ua950.003-391 (Box 5, Folder 81)
- Carpenter, David O., Undated; nam_ua950.003-392 (Box 5, Folder 82)
- Carpenter, David O., Undated; nam_ua950.003-393 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Carpenter, Michael, Undated; nam_ua950.003-394 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Carino, Christine, Undated; nam_ua950.003-395 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Carr, Carson, Undated; nam_ua950.003-396 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Carlos, Alberto J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-397 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Carlson, Bonnie, Undated; nam_ua950.003-398 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Carmack, Robert M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-399 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Caroll, David G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-400 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Carpenter, Allen W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-401 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Carroll, Nan, Undated; nam_ua950.003-402 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Carson, Joanne, Undated; nam_ua950.003-403 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Carter, James A., 1974; nam_ua950.003-404 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Carrino, Elnora, Undated; nam_ua950.003-405 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Carrino, Frank G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-406 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Cartmell, Robert, Undated; nam_ua950.003-407 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Casabone, Jeniffer Orton, Undated; nam_ua950.003-408 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Cascio, Salvatore, Undated; nam_ua950.003-409 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Casey, Jessica A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-410 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Cassaigne, Ella, 1966-1967; nam_ua950.003-411 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Cassanova, Aldo, 1981; nam_ua950.003-412 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Casserly, Mary, Undated; nam_ua950.003-413 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Casserly, Mary F., 2001; nam_ua950.003-414 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Castagnino, Raul, Undated; nam_ua950.003-415 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Castagnino, Raul H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-416 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Castillo, Raymond A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-417 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Castracane, James, Undated; nam_ua950.003-418 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Castracane, James, Undated; nam_ua950.003-419 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Catalano, Lia, Undated; nam_ua950.003-420 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Caticha, Ariel, Undated; nam_ua950.003-421 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Cavanaugh, Barry, Undated; nam_ua950.003-422 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Cawelti, John, Undated; nam_ua950.003-423 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Cermack, Ethel, Undated; nam_ua950.003-424 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Cerri, Richard D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-425 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Cervini, Lori A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-426 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Chadabe, Joel, Undated; nam_ua950.003-427 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Chadabe, Joel, Undated; nam_ua950.003-428 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Chaiken, Seth, Undated; nam_ua950.003-429 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Champagne, Audrey, Undated; nam_ua950.003-430 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Champagne, Audrey, Undated; nam_ua950.003-431 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Champagne, Jane, Undated; nam_ua950.003-432 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Champagne, Kevin, Undated; nam_ua950.003-433 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Chan, Wing Ming, Undated; nam_ua950.003-434 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Chandra, Uday, Undated; nam_ua950.003-435 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Chang, Jane C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-436 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Chang, Julius S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-437 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Chang, Shirley, Undated; nam_ua950.003-438 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Chapel House, 1985-1995; nam_ua950.003-439 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Chapman, David W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-440 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Chapman, Dennis, Undated; nam_ua950.003-441 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Chapman, Sara, Undated; nam_ua950.003-442 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Charnews, Joan, Undated; nam_ua950.003-443 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Chartock, Alan, Undated; nam_ua950.003-444 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Chatterton, Robert G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-445 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Chen, Chan-Fu, Undated; nam_ua950.003-446 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Chen, Kuan I., Undated; nam_ua950.003-447 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Chen, Yu-Hui, 2006; nam_ua950.003-448 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Chen, Yu-Shih, Undated; nam_ua950.003-449 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Cheng, Leida, Undated; nam_ua950.003-450 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Cheng, Pei-Kai, Undated; nam_ua950.003-451 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Cheng, Roger, Undated; nam_ua950.003-452 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Cheng, Roger J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-453 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Chepaitis, Barbara, Undated; nam_ua950.003-454 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Chernaivsky, Michael, 1972 August 20-1973 June; nam_ua950.003-455 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Cherubini, Jon, Undated; nam_ua950.003-456 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Chessin, Henry, Undated; nam_ua950.003-457 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Chesin, Sorrel, Undated; nam_ua950.003-458 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Chesin, Sorrel, Undated; nam_ua950.003-459 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Chi, Benjamin Exner, Undated; nam_ua950.003-460 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Childers, Wesley J., 1941-1963; nam_ua950.003-461 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Childs, John L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-462 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Childs, Lindsay N., Undated; nam_ua950.003-463 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Childs, Lindsay N., Undated; nam_ua950.003-464 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Childs, Lindsay N., Undated; nam_ua950.003-465 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Chisholm, Michael E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-466 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Chisolm, S.W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-467 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Chittur, Sridar, Undated; nam_ua950.003-468 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Chiuchiolo, Nicholas, Undated; nam_ua950.003-469 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Chou, Chien-Fu, Undated; nam_ua950.003-470 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Chow, Julian, Undated; nam_ua950.003-471 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Christenson, Elia H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-472 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Michael N. Christakis, Undated; nam_ua950.003-473 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Christianson, Scott, Undated; nam_ua950.003-474 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Christie, Leona, Undated; nam_ua950.003-475 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Christensen, Edward, Undated; nam_ua950.003-476 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Christodulu, Kristin, Undated; nam_ua950.003-477 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Christoff, Patrick L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-478 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Chui, Sin-Tat, Undated; nam_ua950.003-479 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Chun, Elsie, Undated; nam_ua950.003-480 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Chung, Ling, Undated; nam_ua950.003-481 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Church, Thomas W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-482 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Chylek, Peter, Undated; nam_ua950.003-483 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Cimini, Delores, Undated; nam_ua950.003-484 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Ciompi, Arturo, Undated; nam_ua950.003-485 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Cioppa, Anne, Undated; nam_ua950.003-486 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Cipperly, Joan, Undated; nam_ua950.003-487 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Cipriano, Ramon J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-488 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Claiborne, Nancy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-489 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Clark, Richard M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-490 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Clarkin, William H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-491 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Clas, Carol Ann, Undated; nam_ua950.003-492 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Clausen, Ralph G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-493 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Clogston, A.M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-494 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Closson, William, 1934; nam_ua950.003-495 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Clyman, Toby W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-496 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Cobane, Edith M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-497 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Coburn, Judy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-498 (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Cochran, David H., 1828-1909; nam_ua950.003-499 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- Cochran, John C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-500 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- Cochrane, James, Undated; nam_ua950.003-501 (Box 7, Folder 56)
- Cockrell, Findlay, Undated; nam_ua950.003-502 (Box 7, Folder 57)
- Cockrell, Findlay, Undated; nam_ua950.003-503 (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Cocks, Peter, Undated; nam_ua950.003-504 (Box 7, Folder 59)
- Cocks, Peter G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-505 (Box 7, Folder 60)
- Cody, Evelyn, Undated; nam_ua950.003-506 (Box 7, Folder 61)
- Cody, Michael, Undated; nam_ua950.003-507 (Box 7, Folder 62)
- Coe, Richard (Rick) S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-508 (Box 7, Folder 63)
- Coffey, Martin J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-509 (Box 7, Folder 64)
- Coffey, Martin J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-510 (Box 7, Folder 65)
- Cognon, Jacques, Undated; nam_ua950.003-511 (Box 7, Folder 66)
- Coco, Raymond P., Undated; nam_ua950.003-512 (Box 7, Folder 67)
- Cohen, Donald L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-513 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Cohen, Fred, Undated; nam_ua950.003-514 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Cohen, Fred, Undated; nam_ua950.003-515 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Cohen, Jeffrey, Undated; nam_ua950.003-516 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Cohen, Tom, Undated; nam_ua950.003-517 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Cohon, Rachel, Undated; nam_ua950.003-518 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Colby, Frances L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-519 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Colello, Joseph, Undated; nam_ua950.003-520 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Colemn, Marion Moore, Undated; nam_ua950.003-521 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Colfer, Carmelinda, Undated; nam_ua950.003-522 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Collier, Carolin, Undated; nam_ua950.003-523 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Collier, Mary Beth, Undated; nam_ua950.003-524 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Collier, Naon D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-525 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Collier, Naon D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-526 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Collins, Arthur N., Undated; nam_ua950.003-527 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Collins, Evan R., 1984 May 19; nam_ua950.003-528 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Collins, Jack B., Undated; nam_ua950.003-529 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Collins, James, Undated; nam_ua950.003-530 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Collins, Jefferey L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-531 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Collins, Mark S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-532 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Collins, Mary, Undated; nam_ua950.003-533 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Colman, Charles Wilson, Undated; nam_ua950.003-534 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Colpitts, Phyllis A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-535 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Colquhoun, William R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-536 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Comproski, Kimberly, Undated; nam_ua950.003-537 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Conaway, O.B., Undated; nam_ua950.003-538 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Conboy, Regina, Undated; nam_ua950.003-539 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Condon, William, Undated; nam_ua950.003-540 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Conklin, Douglas, Undated; nam_ua950.003-541 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Conley. Thomas N., Undated; nam_ua950.003-542 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Connelly, Joseph P., Undated; nam_ua950.003-543 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Connophy, Peter F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-544 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Conway, John, Undated; nam_ua950.003-545 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Cook, Earl, Undated; nam_ua950.003-546 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Cooper, Frank, 1964; nam_ua950.003-547 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Cooper, Philip J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-548 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Cooper, Philip J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-549 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Cooren, Francois, Undated; nam_ua950.003-550 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Corbett, Diane, Undated; nam_ua950.003-551 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Corbett, James W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-552 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Corbin, Alice, Undated; nam_ua950.003-553 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Cornet, Florencia, Undated; nam_ua950.003-554 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Corning, Erastus, Undated; nam_ua950.003-555 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Cornish, Alicia R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-556 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Corso, Michael, Undated; nam_ua950.003-557 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Cotton, William R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-558 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Courington, Geri, Undated; nam_ua950.003-559 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Countermine, William A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-560 (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Covington, Sim, Undated; nam_ua950.003-561 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Cowan, L. Gray, Undated; nam_ua950.003-562 (Box 8, Folder 50)
- Cowley, Edward, Undated; nam_ua950.003-563 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Cowling, Vincent F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-564 (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Cowling, Vincent J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-565 (Box 8, Folder 53)
- Cox, George, Undated; nam_ua950.003-566 (Box 8, Folder 54)
- Craig, Hardin, Undated; nam_ua950.003-567 (Box 8, Folder 55)
- Craig, Randall T., Undated; nam_ua950.003-568 (Box 8, Folder 56)
- Craighead, John J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-569 (Box 8, Folder 57)
- Creegan, Robert, Undated; nam_ua950.003-570 (Box 8, Folder 58)
- Cresswell, Anthony M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-571 (Box 8, Folder 59)
- Croasdale, Caroline, Undated; nam_ua950.003-572 (Box 8, Folder 60)
- Cromack, Theodore, Undated; nam_ua950.003-573 (Box 8, Folder 61)
- Cross, Robert, Undated; nam_ua950.003-574 (Box 8, Folder 62)
- Crowley, James, Undated; nam_ua950.003-575 (Box 8, Folder 63)
- Crowley, James A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-576 (Box 8, Folder 64)
- Crull, Harry Edward, 1965-1972 April 25; nam_ua950.003-577 (Box 9, Folder 65)
- Cruz, Jose, Undated; nam_ua950.003-578 (Box 8, Folder 66)
- Cue, Nelson, 1970; nam_ua950.003-579 (Box 8, Folder 67)
- Cully, Thomas, Undated; nam_ua950.003-580 (Box 8, Folder 68)
- Cully, Thomas, Undated; nam_ua950.003-581 (Box 8, Folder 69)
- Cummings John Carey, Undated; nam_ua950.003-582 (Box 8, Folder 70)
- Cummings, Paul A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-583 (Box 8, Folder 71)
- Cundy, Donald, Undated; nam_ua950.003-584 (Box 8, Folder 72)
- Cunninghan, Richard P., Undated; nam_ua950.003-585 (Box 8, Folder 73)
- Cunningham, Veronica, 1992; nam_ua950.003-586 (Box 8, Folder 74)
- Cupoli, Ed, Undated; nam_ua950.003-587 (Box 8, Folder 75)
- Curry, Deborah, 1989-1995; nam_ua950.003-588 (Box 8, Folder 76)
- Curtis, Thomas E, Undated; nam_ua950.003-589 (Box 8, Folder 77)
- Curtis, Thomas E, Undated; nam_ua950.003-590 (Box 8, Folder 78)
- Cushman, Donald P., Undated; nam_ua950.003-591 (Box 8, Folder 79)
- Cusick, Roger, Undated; nam_ua950.003-592 (Box 8, Folder 80)
- Cutler, Gary, Undated; nam_ua950.003-593 (Box 8, Folder 81)
- Cutler, Gary, Undated; nam_ua950.003-594 (Box 8, Folder 82)
- Cuttler, Brian, Undated; nam_ua950.003-595 (Box 8, Folder 83)
- Czapski, Ulrich, Undated; nam_ua950.003-596 (Box 8, Folder 84)
- Dabrowski, Romuald, Undated; nam_ua950.003-597 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- D'ambra, Thomas, Undated; nam_ua950.003-598 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- D'Andrea, Frank, Undated; nam_ua950.003-599 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Daims, Diva Barachini, Undated; nam_ua950.003-600 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Dale, Mark, Undated; nam_ua950.003-601 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Daly, Lawrence Henry, Undated; nam_ua950.003-602 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Dalton, Mark, Undated; nam_ua950.003-603 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- D'Amello, Joseph, Undated; nam_ua950.003-604 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Damhof, Sandra, Undated; nam_ua950.003-605 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Dandridge, Thomas C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-606 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Danese, Gino, Undated; nam_ua950.003-607 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Daniel, Betty C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-608 (Folder 12)
- Daniel, Charles E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-609 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Daniels, Mina H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-610 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Daniels, Thomas, Undated; nam_ua950.003-611 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Danielson, Lucig, Undated; nam_ua950.003-612 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Cummings-Danson, Gail, Undated; nam_ua950.003-613 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Dapo, Donald, Undated; nam_ua950.003-614 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Darbyshire, Sue, Undated; nam_ua950.003-615 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Das, Tara P., Undated; nam_ua950.003-616 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Dascher, Alfred, Undated; nam_ua950.003-617 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Dascal, Neal, Undated; nam_ua950.003-618 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- D'attilo, Michael, Undated; nam_ua950.003-619 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Davidson, Justine A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-620 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Davidowicz, Lucy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-621 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Davis, Edward D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-622 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Davis, Liane, Undated; nam_ua950.003-623 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Davis, Lydia, Undated; nam_ua950.003-624 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Davis, Phillip, Undated; nam_ua950.003-625 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Dawes, Sharon, Undated; nam_ua950.003-626 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Day, Stephen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-627 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Dean, D.E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-628 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Deane, Glenn, Undated; nam_ua950.003-629 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Dear, Gary, Undated; nam_ua950.003-630 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Dearstyne, Bruce William, Undated; nam_ua950.003-631 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- DeBlasi, Anthony, Undated; nam_ua950.003-632 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Decker, Sidney, Undated; nam_ua950.003-633 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Decker, Walter Cornell, Undated; nam_ua950.003-634 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Dedrick, Blanchard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-635 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- deGonzague, Arleen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-636 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Dehais, Richard J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-637 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Deiber, Gwen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-638 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Deininger, Richard C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-639 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- De La Foret, Peggy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-640 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- DeLaMater, Christine, Undated; nam_ua950.003-641 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- DeLamater, Claudette R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-642 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Delano, John, Undated; nam_ua950.003-643 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Delano, John, Undated; nam_ua950.003-644 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- D'elia, Christopher, Undated; nam_ua950.003-645 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Dehong, Dennis, Undated; nam_ua950.003-646 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Delong, Stephen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-647 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Delio, Vincent, Undated; nam_ua950.003-648 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- DelAanto, John H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-649 (Box 9, Folder 53)
- Deluca, Nicholas, Undated; nam_ua950.003-650 (Box 9, Folder 54)
- Demacario, Everly Conway, Undated; nam_ua950.003-651 (Box 9, Folder 55)
- Dembowski, Frederick L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-652 (Box 9, Folder 56)
- Demerjian, Kenneth L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-653 (Box 9, Folder 57)
- DeMeo, Joseph, Undated; nam_ua950.003-654 (Box 9, Folder 58)
- Debeneaux, Gregory, Undated; nam_ua950.003-655 (Box 9, Folder 59)
- Dennis, Livia, Undated; nam_ua950.003-656 (Box 9, Folder 60)
- Dennis, Margaret A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-657 (Box 9, Folder 61)
- Denton, Nancy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-658 (Box 9, Folder 62)
- De Pasquale, Brian, Undated; nam_ua950.003-659 (Box 9, Folder 63)
- Derrick, Virginia J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-660 (Box 9, Folder 64)
- Derrick, William, Undated; nam_ua950.003-661 (Box 9, Folder 65)
- Derringh, Edward, Undated; nam_ua950.003-662 (Box 9, Folder 66)
- DeSantis, Deiedre, Undated; nam_ua950.003-663 (Box 9, Folder 67)
- DeSantis, Deiedre, Undated; nam_ua950.003-664 (Box 9, Folder 68)
- Desfosses, Helen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-665 (Box 9, Folder 69)
- Desfosses, Helen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-666 (Box 9, Folder 70)
- De Sole, Gloria, Undated; nam_ua950.003-667 (Box 9, Folder 71)
- Dunn, Daniel, Undated; nam_ua950.003-668 (Box 9, Folder 72)
- Devane, Mary Anne, Undated; nam_ua950.003-669 (Box 9, Folder 73)
- Dewey, John F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-670 (Box 9, Folder 74)
- Dewey, John N., Undated; nam_ua950.003-671 (Box 9, Folder 75)
- Dewitt-Parker, Joyce, Undated; nam_ua950.003-672 (Box 9, Folder 76)
- Diamond, William M., 1969; nam_ua950.003-673 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Dickey, James M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-674 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Dickinson, Joanne, Undated; nam_ua950.003-675 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Didier, Maureen C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-676 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- DiDionna, Michelle, Undated; nam_ua950.003-677 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Dieffenback, Bruce, Undated; nam_ua950.003-678 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Gigiorgio, Diane, 1980; nam_ua950.003-679 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Dillon, Harold Joseph, 1965-1974; nam_ua950.003-680 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Dineen, Richard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-681 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Dinovo, Robert, Undated; nam_ua950.003-682 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Dirocco-Ruskin, Valerie, Undated; nam_ua950.003-683 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- DiSteffano, Jacqeline S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-684 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- DoBell, Howard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-685 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Dobson, Michael W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-686 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Docksai, Ronald F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-687 (Box 10, Folder 15)